A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 2, Accession 2017:058 FA1393
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 2, Accession 2017:058
1967-2011
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation
FA1393
38.26 Cubic Feet 85 boxes: 84 letter-sized document boxes, 1 record storage box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
All inquiries to view films require advanced notice of at least 2 business days, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those that are not available in modern formats, may be restricted from access at the discretion of RAC.
Biographical / Historical
The Henry Luce Foundation was established by Henry R. Luce in 1936. As a New York-based nonprofit organization, the Luce Foundation awards grants in American Art, Asian studies, Higher Education, Theology, and supports the Clare Boothe Luce Program for women in science, mathematics, and engineering.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Henry Luce Foundation in 2017.
Related Materials
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 1, Accession 2017:057 (FA1317)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 3, Accession 2017:059 (FA1410)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 4, Accession 2017:060 (FA1442)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 5, Accession 2017:061 (FA1472)
Arrangement
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 2) are arranged as follows:
Series 1: Project Files, 1978-2011
Series 2: Professorship Files, 1967-2004
Series 3: United States-China Cooperative Research Program, 1975-2010
Series 4: Asset Management and Financial Files, 1986-1990
Scope and Contents
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 2) consists primarily of grant and professorship files. There is also a substantial amount of material regarding the Luce Foundation's Asia Program including files on the United States-China Cooperative Research program and the Luce Scholars program.
Art, American; International economic relations -- Research grants -- South Asia; Education (Higher); Theology -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; United States--Relations--China
- Project Files, 1978-2011; 1
  - Academy of American Poets - Benefit Events, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Acting Company - The Cornell Project, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Alban Institute - Leadership Initiative, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - The Albrecht-Kemper Museum of Art - Catalog of Permanent Collection (ACE), 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Albright-Knox Art Gallery - Edwin Dickson, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alliance of New York State Arts Council, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alliance Theological Seminary - Chinese Library Research Center, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Program Council for Independent Schools, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Academy of Religion, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Academy of Religion - Workshop for Training Theological Educators, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - American Alliance for Rights and Responsibilities - Chairman's Award: Second Printing of The Winnable War, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Alliance for Rights and Responsibilities - Community Peace and Order Defense, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - American Assembly, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - American Association of Museums, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - American Ballet Monuments Commission - National World War II Memorial, 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - American Council on Capital Formation: Center for Policy Research, 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 503)
  - American Council on Capital Formation: Center for Policy Research, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - American Council on Capital Formation: Center for Policy Research - Public Education Program, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1980-1984 (Box 67, Folder 504)
  - American Council of Learned Societies - Art History Fellowships, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 21-24)
  - American Council of Learned Societies - Dissertation Program in American Art, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
  - American Council of Learned Societies - Research Conference and Volume Series, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (University Service Center), 1980-1988 (Box 67, Folder 505)
  - American Council for the United Nations University - Operating Costs, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1982-1986 (Box 67, Folder 506)
  - American Enterprise Institute and the Brookings Institute - Congressional Seminar #7, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research - China and Most Favored Nation Issue, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - American Foreign Service Association - United States Foreign Policy Conference, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - American Friends of Canada - David Milne Project, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - American Judicature Society, 1982-1988 (Box 67, Folder 507)
  - American Russian Young Artists Orchestra - Residencies Training and Two World Tours, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - American Textile History Museum - Textile Art from Southern Appalachia, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - American Theological Library Association - Digitization Project, 2000-2006 (Box 5, Folder 35-36)
  - Americans for the Arts - Arts and Religion Project Publication, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Americans for the Arts - Conference with National Assembly of State Art Agencies, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Amon Carter Museum, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Appalachian Ministries Educational Resource Center - Portraits in Regional Pluralism, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Appalachian Ministries Educational Resource Center - Theology, Farming and Ecology Program, 1994-2005 (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
  - Archives of American Art, 1982-1993 (Box 67, Folder 508)
  - The Asia Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 43-44)
  - The Asia Foundation - American Studies in Vietnam, 2004-2009 (Box 67, Folder 509)
  - The Asia Foundation - America's Role in Asia, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - The Asia Foundation - Asia Pacific Philanthropy Consortium, 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 46-47)
  - The Asia Society - China Council, 1978-1982 (Box 68, Folder 510)
  - The Asia Society - Luce Foundation Conference Room, 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 511)
  - The Asia Society - Mandela: Architecture of Enlightenment, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - The Asia Society - Museum Internship Program in Asian Art, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - The Asia Society - Renovate Henry Luce Conference Room, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Asian American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1982-1985 (Box 68, Folder 512)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Asian Art Fellowship Program, 1994-2006 (Box 8, Folder 51-52)
  - ASIANetwork - Book, Website, Newsletter, and Conference, 1997-2000 (Box 68, Folder 513)
  - ASIANetwork - Teaching of Asian Students at Liberal Arts Colleges, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 53-54)
  - The Aspen Institute - China Symposium on Legal Protection of Human Rights, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - The Aspen Institute - Congressional Program on China, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 56-57)
  - Association for Asian Studies - Asia Scholars at 1996 Annual Meeting, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Association for Asian Studies - Harry Benda Prize in Southeast Asian Studies, 1996-2003 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - The Association for Religion and Intellectual Life - Consultations on Religion in Higher Education, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 60-61)
  - The Association for Religion and Intellectual Life - Scholars-in-Residence Program, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Association of Theological Schools, 1981-1987 (Box 68, Folder 514)
  - Association to Unite the Democracies - The New Centure Conference, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States - US-China-Taiwan Cross-Strait Dialogue, 2005-2011 (Box 68, Folder 515)
  - Australian National University - American Scholars of Southeast Asia, 2000-2008 (Box 68, Folder 516)
  - Australian National University - Doctoral and Post-Doctoral Scholars, 1998-2011 (Box 69, Folder 517)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art - Theodore Robinson: The Giverny Works, 2002-2005 (Box 69, Folder 518)
  - Barnes Foundation, 2001-2011 (Box 69, Folder 519-520)
  - Beaver College - Catherine and Harry Kuch Recreation and Athletic Center, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Berkeley Art Museum - A Rose Has No Teeth: Bruce Nauman's Formative Years, 2005-2008 (Box 69, Folder 521)
  - Birmingham-Southern College - Center for Leadership Studies, 1993-1997 (Box 10, Folder 65-66)
  - Jack S. Blanton Museum of Art - Michener Collection of 20th Century Art, 1998-2011 (Box 70, Folder 522)
  - Boston University - International Center for East Asian Archaeology, 1999-2011 (Box 70, Folder 523-524)
  - The Boy's Club of New York - Reconstructing of Flushing, Queens Club, 1992-1999 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Broad Jump, 1983-1985 (Box 70, Folder 525)
  - Brookings Institution, 1981-1984 (Box 70, Folder 526)
  - Brookings Institution - Center for Asian-Pacific Studies, 1997-2000 (Box 71, Folder 527)
  - Brooklyn Museum - Kindred Spirits: Asher B. Durand and the American Landscape, 2005-2008 (Box 71, Folder 528)
  - The Brooklyn Children's Museum - Community Service Program, 1992-1997 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - The Brooklyn Museum - Cleaning, Conservation, and Framing of Mignot's Niagara, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - The Brooklyn Museum - Promotion of Thomas Cole Show in New York, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - The Brooklyn Museum - Thomas Cole: Landscape into History, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Byzantine Fresco Foundation, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - John Carter Brown Library - Catalog of American Imprints before 1800, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 73-74)
  - The Catholic University of America, 1983-1987 (Box 71, Folder 529)
  - The Catholic University of America - Paul Weiss Symposium, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 530)
  - Center for the Arts, Religion and Education - Visual Arts Conference, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Center for Immigration Studies - Income Disparity and Job Displacement, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Center of Theological Inquiry - Colloquium on Calvinism and Visual Arts, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Center of Theological Inquiry - Professor Finney's Research, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - The Chi Psi Educational Trust - National Leadership Training Program, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - The China Institute, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - China Institute in America - Management and Business Development Program, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - The China Institute - Matching Challenge Grant, 1974-1983 (Box 71, Folder 531)
  - China Institute in America - Photo Exhibition: Between China and Tibet, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Chinatown Planning Council, 1982-1985 (Box 71, Folder 532)
  - Christian Arts Inc. - Complete Hines Opera: "I Am the Way", 1992 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks - Website Upgrade, 1997-2008 (Box 71, Folder 533-534)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Folder 534 is closed - contains personnel material.
  - Cincinnati Art Museum - Cincinnati Artists Collection, 2002-2008 (Box 72, Folder 535-536)
  - Cities in Schools, 1982-1983 (Box 72, Folder 537)
  - Citizens Budget Committee, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 538)
  - Claremont University Center and Graduate School - Humanities Center, 1992-1997 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - College Art Association, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 86-87)
  - College Art Association - Professional Development Fellowships, 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Columbia University East Asian Institute - Pacific Basin Studies Program (Renewal), 1989-1993 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Columbia University Graduate School of Business - Sustainable Development Initiatives, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Community Preparatory School, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Connecticut College - Center for International Studies and Liberal Arts, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - The Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art - Infrastructure Institute, 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Coro Foundation, 1983-1986 (Box 72, Folder 539)
  - Coro Foundation - Leadership New York, 1991-1996 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - The Corporation for Thomas Jefferson's Poplar Forest - Restoration of Poplar Forest, 1993-1999 (Box 14, Folder 95-96)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Asia and United States-Asia Relations Seminars, 1992-1997 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Council on International Educational Exchange - Southeast Asia Programs, 1989-1994 (Box 14, Folder 98-99)
  - Detroit Institute of the Arts - American Art Collection, 2005-2008 (Box 72, Folder 540)
  - Detroit Institute of the Arts - Re-installation DVD (Box 72, Folder 540)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Dia Art Foundation - Dan Flavin: A Retrospective, 2004-2006 (Box 73, Folder 541)
  - The Door, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Duke University - Asian/Pacific Studies Institute, 1992-1997 (Box 15, Folder 101-102)
  - The Dwelling Place of New York, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - East-West Center - Confucianism and Human Rights Conference, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - East-West Center - Political Authority and Legitimacy in Southeast Asia, 1992-2011 (Box 73, Folder 542)
  - Economic Strategy Institute, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Education Testing Services, 1983-1988 (Box 73, Folder 543)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, 1983-1986 (Box 73, Folder 544)
  - Elvehjem Museum of Art - John Steuart Curry Exhibit, 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 106-107)
  - English Language Advocates, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Executive Council on Foreign Diplomats, 1983-1987 (Box 73, Folder 545-546)
  - Fort Wayne Museum of Art - Alma Thomas Exhibition, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 109-110)
  - The Foundation Center, 1981-1985 (Box 74, Folder 547)
  - The Foundation Center - Library and Information Services Support, 1992-1999 (Box 16, Folder 111-112)
  - Foundation for the Performing Arts - Colleen Moore Memorial Fund, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 114-115)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - High School Teachers Economics Seminar, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - Leadership Retreat, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 117-118)
  - Franklin Furnace - Avant-Garde New York, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 119-120)
  - The Fresh Air Fund - Career Awareness Program, 1994-1997 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Frick Art Reference Library, 1993-2000 (Box 17, Folder 122-123)
  - Fund for Theological Education - Ministry Programs, 2003-2007 (Box 74, Folder 548-549)
  - Gallery Association of New York State - Studio Museum in Harlem: 25 Years of African American Art, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 124-125)
  - George Washington University - International Law Program, National University of Laos, 2004-2006 (Box 74, Folder 550)
  - Georgetown University - Program in Southeast Asian Studies, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 126)
  - Georgetown University - Southeast Asia Survey, 2002-2011 (Box 74, Folder 551)
  - Georgetown University - Southeast Asian Studies Center (Renewal), 1998-2011 (Box 74, Folder 552)
  - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 127)
  - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York - ClubZOOM Engineering Program and the Design and Discovery Program, 2007-2008 (Box 75, Folder 553)
  - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York - ClubZOOM Engineering Program and the Design and Discovery Program (Box 75, Folder 553)
  - Good Shepherd Services, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 128)
  - Graduate Theological Union, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 129)
  - Graduate Theological Union - Andy Warhol Research Project, 1993-1999 (Box 18, Folder 130)
  - Grand Street Settlement, 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - The Hale Foundation - Enhancement of Undergraduate Experience, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Harvard University Divinity School, 1983-1990 (Box 75, Folder 554)
  - Harvard University - Graduate School of Education, 1979-1985 (Box 75, Folder 555)
  - The Healthcare Chaplaincy, 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts, 1979-1982 (Box 75, Folder 556)
  - Human Rights Watch (Asia Watch) - Internship Program, 1992-1997 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - Hunter College, 1981-1983 (Box 75, Folder 557)
  - Iona Senior Services - Resource Library in Wellness Center, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - International Campaign for Tibet - "Chinese Scholars on Tibet" English Translation, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art (University of Pennsylvania) - Andres Serrano Catalog Reprinting, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  - Institute of Museum Services - Museum Leadership Initiatives Program, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - Stanley M. Isaacs Neighborhood Center, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 139)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange, 1983-1986 (Box 75, Folder 558)
  - Japan Society Inc., 1993-1998 (Box 19, Folder 140-141)
  - Judson Memorial Church - LaFarge Stained Glass Windows, 1995-2000 (Box 20, Folder 142)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1994-1998 (Box 20, Folder 143-144)
  - Legionaries of Christ - Costs of Two Seminarians, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 145)
  - Lehman College Art Gallery - Public Art in the Bronx, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 146)
  - Library of Congress - Jefferson, Knowledge and Democracy, 1993-1996 (Box 21, Folder 147)
  - Library of Congress Congressional Research Service - Congressional Retreats and Seminars, 1991-1996 (Box 21, Folder 148)
  - The Living Pulpit, Inc. - Direct Mail Promotion Effort, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 149)
  - The Living Pulpit, Inc. - Subsidized Subscriptions for Seminarians, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 150)
  - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 559)
  - Luce Scholars Program, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 560-563)
  - Lutheran Educational Conference of North America - China Seminar and Exchange Program, 1993-1997 (Box 21, Folder 151)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club - Educational Outreach Program, 1993-1996 (Box 21, Folder 152-153)
  - Marietta College, 1993-1998 (Box 21, Folder 154-155)
  - Mepkin Abbey - Ecumenical Chapel Pipe Organ and Bell Tower, 1993-1998 (Box 22, Folder 156)
  - Merry-Go-Round Museum, Inc. - Gustav Dentzel Exhibition, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 157)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1993-1999 (Box 22, Folder 158-159)
  - Michigan State University, 1982-1988 (Box 76, Folder 564)
  - National Academy of Public Administration, 1981-1987 (Box 77, Folder 565)
  - National Association of Endowed Presbyterian Churches (NAEPC) - Investment Guidance Policy, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 160)
  - National Committee on United States-China Relations, 1981-1984 (Box 77, Folder 566)
  - National Committee on United States-China Relations - United States and Changing Greater China, 1992-1997 (Box 22, Folder 161-162)
  - National Council of Christians and Jews, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 567)
  - National Council of Christians and Jews - Theology in Pluralistic Setting (Renewal), 1989-1997 (Box 23, Folder 163-164)
  - National Council of Foreign Languages and International Studies, 1983-1985 (Box 77, Folder 568)
  - National Cultural Alliance - Arts Public Awareness Campaign, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 165-166)
    - The Advertising Council Arts and Humanities Campaign, undated; inch audio cassette (Box T1)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - National Cultural Alliance - National Arts Campaign (Renewal), 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 167)
  - National Executive Service Corps, 1981-1983 (Box 77, Folder 569)
  - National Humanities Center, 1981-1986 (Box 77, Folder 570)
  - National Retiree Volunteer Center, 1993-1998 (Box 24, Folder 168-169)
  - National Taiwan University, 1982-1983 (Box 77, Folder 571)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Historic Landscape Initiative, 1992-1998 (Box 24, Folder 170-171)
  - Nativity Mission Center, 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 172)
  - New York City Mission Society - New York City Bible Institutes Accreditation, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 173)
  - New York City Police Foundation, Inc. - Police Integrity Training Program, 1994-1998 (Box 25, Folder 174-175)
  - The New-York Historical Society - General Operations, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 176)
  - New York Landmarks Conservancy - Sacred Sites Program, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 177-178)
  - New York Public Library, 1981-1986 (Box 78, Folder 572)
  - The New York Studio School - Gallery Exhibition Program, 1991-1996 (Box 26, Folder 179)
  - New York Theological Seminary, 1982-1985 (Box 78, Folder 573)
  - New York Urban League, 1973-1984 (Box 78, Folder 574)
  - The 1990 Institute - Projects on China's Economic Reform, 1990-1996 (Box 26, Folder 180)
  - Northern Illinois University - Burma Studies Group Colloquium, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 181)
  - Northwest China Council - Symposium on American Missions and Social Change in China, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 182)
  - Norton Gallery of Art - American Collections Catalog, 1991-1998 (Box 26, Folder 183)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Centers of America, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 575)
  - Pan American Development Foundation (PADF) - Project Director for CAFED, 1993-1997 (Box 26, Folder 184)
  - The Parrish Art Museum - Paintings and Patronage: 10th Street Studios, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 185)
  - Partners for Sacred Places - Building New Partnerships for America, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 186-187)
  - Peabody Essex Museum - Samuel McIntire: Carving an American Style, 2004-2008 (Box 78, Folder 576-577)
  - Pennsylvania State University - Evolutionary Models of Social and Economic Behavior, 1997-2004 (Box 79, Folder 578)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Hon'ami Koetsu: Japanese Renaissance Master, 1999-2011 (Box 79, Folder 579)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Ikeno Taiga, 2004-2011 (Box 79, Folder 580)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Patronage of the Cadwalader Family, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 188)
  - Phillips Academy, 1991-1996 (Box 27, Folder 189)
  - Police Athletic League - In-School Training and Employment Program, 2006-2011 (Box 79, Folder 581)
  - Pratt Institute - Program in Responsible Creativity, 1990-1994 (Box 27, Folder 190)
  - Prep for Prep - Public Affairs Initiative of Leadership Development, 1991-1996 (Box 27, Folder 191)
  - Price Tower Arts Center - American Architecture Study Center, 2005-2007 (Box 79, Folder 582)
  - Public Conversations Project - Local Interfaith Initiatives, 2003-2004 (Box 79, Folder 583)
  - Redwood Library and Anthenaeum - Van Alen Gallery, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 584)
  - Research Libraries Group - Catalog of Rare Chinese Books (Renewal), 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 192)
  - Rose Art Museum (Brandeis University) - More than Minimal: Women's Work in the 70's, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 193)